#### Contact

4436905452 (Mobile) nursekellyk@att.net

www.linkedin.com/in/kelly-king-msn-rn-cnml-ne-bc-b0979080 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Excel Management

# Kelly King, MSN, RN, CNML NE-BC

Nurse Director/Nurse Manager Critical Care and Emergency Services

Fort Worth, Texas

### Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Vital Signs, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Team Building, and Healthcare Information Technology (HIT). Strong healthcare services professional with a RN to MSN focused in Emergency Room/Trauma Nursing/ Nurse Executive from Western Governors University.

#### Experience

Texas Health Resources
Registered Nurse
October 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months)
Denton, Texas

Tarrant County ENA
Tarrant County ENA Secretary
October 2016 - Present (3 years 10 months)

Baylor Scott & White Health Careers Registered Nurse Critical Care July 2014 - Present (6 years 1 month) Grapevine, Texas

University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center Registered Nurse Critical Care Float Pool November 2012 - July 2014 (1 year 9 months) Dallas, Texas

Critical Care Professional Staffing Agency Registered Nurse Critical Care September 2005 - October 2012 (7 years 2 months) Page 1 of 2 Baltimore, Maryland

LifeBridge Health
Critical Care Registered Nurse
September 2009 - October 2011 (2 years 2 months)
Baltimore, Maryland Area

University of Maryland Medical Center Registered Nurse Trauma May 2003 - September 2006 (3 years 5 months)

## Education

Western Governors University
RN to MSN, Emergency Room/Trauma Nursing/ Nurse Executive
· (2016 - 2018)

The University of Texas at Arlington
MSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2016)